邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
爸爸
Dad.
萨姆这不是你想象的那么简单
Sam. This is bigger than you think. They're everywhere.
我想他想让我们继续他的工作
He wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
Saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
The family business.
我们得找到爸爸
I gotta find Dad.
我又梦见了杰西卡死之前的样子
l dreamt about Jessica's death before it happened.
你还好吧
You gotta be careful, all right?
鬼魂喜欢招惹那些有心灵感应能力的人
Ghosts are attracted to that ESP thing you got.
不是心灵感应 我只是做了一个奇怪的梦
I told you, it's not ESP. I just have strange vibes.Weird dreams.
人们都会做这种不可思议的梦
People have weird dreams.
我有做过些噩梦 有些变成真的了
I have these nightmares. And sometimes they come true.
真的吗
Come again?
救命 快来人救救我
Help! Somebody help me!
快来人 救救我
Somebody help!
我会在午夜前回家
I'll be home around midnight.
哪一个会为你带来救赎
Which one gonna bring you salvation?
迪恩
Dean.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
现在是半夜
It's the middle of the night.
我们得走了
We have to go.
发生什么事了
What's happening?
我们得走了 马上就走
We have to go. Right now.
我找克雷迪 侦探克雷迪 158分机
McReady. Detective McReady. Badge number 1 58.
我有样东西在480区要你查一下
I've got a signal 480 in progress.
我要查一辆双门车
I need the registered owner of a sedan.
密歇根牌照 玛丽·佛兰克六零三七
Michigan license plate...Mary-Frank-six-zero-three-seven.
好的 就这样 拜托快点
Yeah, okay, just hurry.
萨姆 放轻松
Sammy, relax.
那只是个噩梦而已
I'm sure it's just a nightmare
那你说说看你的理由
Yeah, tell me about it.
我是说 每天都可能会做到噩梦 这很正常
I mean it. A normal, everyday, naked in class nightmare.
这个牌照也查不到什么
This plate won't check out. You'll see.
这次不一样了 迪恩 真的…
It felt different, Dean. Real.
就象那时我梦见杰西卡和老屋一样
Like when I dreamt about our house. And Jessica.
你梦见自己的房子和女朋友 这也不是没有道理啊
Yeah, you were dreaming about our house, your girlfriend.
这次在你梦中的那个家伙 你之前有看见过他吗
This guy, you ever seen him before?
没有
No.
没有 那你怎么知道这家伙在密歇根
No. Exactly. Why would you have premonitions about some random dude?
我也不知道为什么
l don't know.
那我更不可能知道
Me neither.
是的 我在听
Yes, l'm here.
吉姆·米勒 密歇根州萨吉诺市
Jim Miller. Saginaw, Michigan.
你有具体的地址吗
You have a street address?
知道了
Got it.
谢谢
Thanks.
查到了
It checks out.
我们还有多远
How far are we?
- 到吉诺市吗 - 是的
- From Saginaw? - Yeah.
2个多小时吧
A couple hours.
开快点
Drive faster.
《邪恶力量》
发生什么事了
What happened?
自杀
Suicide.
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你认识他吗
Did you know him?
看见他每周日都在圣奥古斯丁教堂
Saw him every Sunday at St. Augustine's.
他看上去…
Always seems.
实在太寻常了
Seemed so normal.
你难以想象 门背后到底发生了什么
You never know what's going on behind closed doors.
无法想象
l guess not.
怎么会的
how did ?
他们说是怎么会发生这事的
How are they saying it happened?
我听说是他们在车库发现了他
I heard they found him in the garage...
他把自己锁在车里 但引擎仍然在转
locked inside his car with the engine running.
你知道他们是什么时候发现他的吗
Do you know what time they found him?
大概就1或2个小时之前吧
It just happened an hour or two ago.
他的家人实在太可怜了
His poor family.
我难以想象她们接下来要怎么过
I can't even imagine what they're going through.
萨姆 我们已经尽快赶到了
Sam, we got here as fast as we could.
但还不够快
Not fast enough.
伙计 我们根本没帮上什么
Which just doesn't make any sense, man.
为什么我之前会有这种预兆
Why have these premonitions...
但还是无法救他
unless there was a chance I could stop them?
我不知道
I don't know.
那你认为是谁杀了他
So, what do you think killed him?
可能这家伙真是自杀
Maybe the guy just killed himself.
可能这根本就不是灵异事件
Maybe there's nothing supernatural going on at all.
我告诉你 我看到了全过程
I'm telling you, I watched it happen.
他是被其他一些东西杀死的
He was murdered by something, Dean.
它们把他困在车库里
It trapped him in the garage.
是幽魂 恶鬼 还是其他什么
Like what? A spirit? A poltergeist?
我不清楚那是什么
I don't know what it was.
我不知道我为什么会做这些梦
I don't know why I'm having the dreams.
迪恩 我不知道到底发生了什么
Dean I don't know what's happening.
你说什么
What?
没什么
Nothing, man.
我只是有点担心你
I'm just I'm worried about you.
别用那种眼神看我
Well, don't look at me like that.
我从不那样看着你
I'm not looking at you like anything.
我不得不说 你看上去很颓废
Though I gotta say, you look like crap.
我没事 谢谢关心
Nice. Thanks.
那好吧
Yeah, well....
走吧 我们早上再来继续调查
Come on, let's just pick this up in the morning, all right?
我们得看一下那房子
We'll check out the house.
和他的家人交谈一翻
W'll talk to the family.
迪恩 你也看到了 他们现在非常难过
Dean, you saw them. They're devastated.
他们不会想和我们谈话的
They're not gonna want to talk to us.
你说的没错
Yeah, you're right.
我想我可能知道 他们可能会和谁谈话
But l think I know who they will talk to.
谁
Who?
看来这是我们新的身份
This has got to be a whole new low for us.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我是西蒙斯神父 这是佛利神父
I'm Father Simmons, this is Father Frehley.
我们是圣奥古斯丁教堂 新来的牧师
We're new junior priests over at St. Augustine's.
我们能进来吗
May we come in?
谢谢 我们对此事非常遗憾
hanks. We're very sorry for your loss.
在这种困难时刻 上帝的引导犹为必要
It's in difficult times when the Lord is most needed.
别用这是上帝的意思来说服我
Look. You wanna pitch your whole "Lord has a plan" thing? Fine.
别跟我来这一套
Don't pitch it to me.
我兄弟死了
My brother's dead.
罗杰 拜托不要这样
Roger, please.
不好意思
Excuse me.
不好意思那是我丈夫的哥哥
I'm sorry about my brother in law.
他对吉姆的死非常难过
He's just so upset about Jim's death.
要不要来些咖啡
Would you like some coffee?
谢谢
That'd be great.
谢谢你们来访
It was wonderful of you to stop by.
也谢谢教堂的关心
The support of the Church means so much right now.
这是应该的
Of course.
不管怎么说 我们都是上帝的孩子
After all, we are all God's children.
怎么了
What?
拜托你装的象点神父
Just tone it down a little bit, Father.
米勒太太 你丈夫之前有没有 显露出情绪低落
So, Ms. Miller, did your husband have a history of depression?
没有这种迹象
Nothing like that.
我们象其他人一样有酸甜苦辣
We had our ups and downs like everyone.
但我们很快乐
But we were happy.
我只是不明白…
I just don't underst
为什么吉姆会这样做…
and how Jim could do something like that.
我很遗憾是你发现了他的尸体
I'm so sorry you had to find him like that.
事实上 是我的儿子 马克斯…
Actually, our son, Max...
是他发现了他的尸体
he was the one who found him.
你是否介意我和他谈谈
Do you mind if maybe I go talk to him?
谢谢你 神父
Oh, thank you, Father.
马克斯
Max?
嘿 我是萨姆
Hey, l'm Sam.
米勒太太 你的屋子不错
Ms. Miller, you have a lovely home.
你们住在这里多久了
How long have you lived here?
我们是5年前搬进来的
We moved in about five years ago.
嗯
Hmm.
这些旧房子应该都会有些问题吧
You know, the only problem with these old houses....
我想你肯定为此感到头痛不已吧
I bet you have all kinds of headaches.
你是指
Like what?
就象漏水 断电
Well, weird leaks, electrical shortages...
夜里有奇怪的声音 这些之类的事情
odd settling noises at night. That kind of thing?
没有 没有象你所说的那些事情
No, nothing like that.
这里很好
It's been perfect.
嗯
Hmm.
那是…
That's....
我能看下你的房间吗
May I use your restroom?
当然可以 就在楼上
Oh, sure. It's just up the stairs.
谢谢
Okay.
你的父亲怎么样
So, what was your dad like?
就象一般的父亲一样
Just a normal dad.
现在你呆在家里吗
ah. And you live You live at home now?
我想去上学 但我做不到
Yeah. I'm trying to save up for school, but it's hard.
当你发现你父亲的尸体时
So when you found your dad....
我醒过来
I woke up.
听见引擎在转
I heard the engine running.
我不知道为什么他这样干
I don't know why he did it.
我知道失去亲人是很痛苦的
I know it's rough losing a parent.
尤其是你还小的时候
Especially when you don't have all the answers.
有什么发现吗
Anything?
没有发现
Zip.
你发现了什么
So, what do you have?
一些没用的东西
Nothing.
自米勒的房子造好以来 没发生什么事
Nothing bad has happened in the house since it was built.
那片地怎么样
The land?
不是墓地
No graveyards
战场部落没发生过什么暴行 也不在宝藏旁边
Battlefields tribal lands or any kind of atrocity on or near the property.
我跟你过说了
I told you.
那屋子我上上下下都搜过了
I searched up and down.
没有阴深的角落 没有硫磺味
There were no cold spots, no sulfur scent, nada.
他的家人都说那里很正常
Family said everything was normal?
如果那有恶鬼
If there was a demon or poltergeist...
你认为他们不会察觉到什么吗
wouldn't somebody notice?
我用红外线热量扫描仪扫过
I used the infrared thermal scanner, man.
什么都没有
There was nothing.
那你认为吉姆是自杀的
So, what, you think Jim Miller killed himself...
而我的梦只是个巧合吗
And my dream was just some sort of freakish coincidence?
我不清楚
I don't know.
但我很确定那屋子里没有什么灵异事件
I'm sure that there's nothing supernatural about that house.
那好吧
Yeah. Well....
但你也明白的 可能那屋子没有什么问题
You know, maybe it has nothing to do with the house.
可能只是一个巧合
ybe it's just Gosh.
也可能和吉姆其他的事有关联
Maybe it's connected to Jim in some other way.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
我的头
Ah! My head!
萨姆
Sam.
嘿
Hey!
发生什么了 快告诉我
What's going on? Talk to me.
它又来了
It's happening again.
它要杀罗杰·米勒
Something's gonna kill Roger Miller.
罗杰·米勒
Roger Miller?
不 只是要地址 谢谢
No, no. Just the address, please.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
西树林450号 1120号公寓
450 West Grove, apartment 1 1 20.
你还好吧
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
如果不行的话 我可以停下来
You hurl, l'll pull over because the upholstery.
我没事 继续开
I'm fine. Drive. All right.
那好吧
All right.
迪恩 我有些害怕
Dean, I'm scared, man.
现在这些噩梦还不算最糟
Nightmares weren't bad enough.
而我醒过来之后就见到 它就这样发生了
Now l'm seeing things while awake?
但这些梦正变的越来越可怕 让人痛苦
And these visions or whatever they're getting more intense and painful.
别太担心了 一切会好的
Come on. lt'll be all right.
你会好的
You'll be fine.
米勒一家怎么了
What is it about the Millers?
为什么我和他们有联系
Why am l connected to them?
为什么我能看到他们死去
Why am l watching them die?
为什么这事发生在我身上
Why is this happening to me?
我真的不知道 萨姆
I don't know.
但我们会查个究竟 好吗
But we'll figure it out.
我们每天都面对着些无法解释的事情
We face the unexplainable every day.
这只是里面的一部分而已
This is just another thing.
不 我们从来没遇到过这种情况
No. It's never been us.
我们家族也没遇到过
It's never been in the family like this.
坦白的告诉我 这事没让你不安吧
Tell the truth. You can't tell me this doesn't freak you out.
没让我不安
This doesn't freak me out.
嘿 罗杰
Hey, Roger!
嘿 等一下
Hey, hold up a second.
你们到底是干什么的 传教士吗
What are you, missionaries?
让我一个人静静
Leave me alone.
等等
Please!
嘿 罗杰 我们只是想帮助你
Hey, Roger! We're trying to help!
等等 嘿…
Please. Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
我不需要你们的帮助
I don't want your help.
我们不是牧师 你得听我们说
We're not priests! Listen to us!
罗杰你现在正身处危险之中
ger You're in danger!
快…
Come on, come on, come on.
在这里
Here.
擦掉你的指纹
Start wiping down your fingerprints.
我不想让警察发现我们来过
We don't want the cops to know we were here.
快走
Go! Go! Come on.
我进去看看
I'm gonna take a look inside.
这里没有什么
There was nothing in there.
没什么特别的 就象米勒的屋子
No signs either, just like the Millers' house.
我有看见一个黑影
I saw something in the vision, like a dark shape.
有些 有些东西正跟着罗杰
mething was Something was stalking Roger.
不管是什么
Whatever it was
我们可以确定这和 他们的屋子无关
It's not connected to their house.
不 这和他们家族有关
No, it's connected to the family itself.
那你是怎么想的
So, what do you think?
难道是复仇的鬼魂
Like a vengeful spirit?
一些缠绕着他们家族的鬼
A few that have been known to latch on to families.
跟着他们已经有好多年了
Follow them for years.
是恶鬼吗 还是妖精
Angiaks, Banshees.
可能是种诅咒
Basically like a curse.
可能罗杰和吉姆卷进了棘手的事
Roger and Jim got involved in something heavy.
和一些被诅咒的事物
Something curse worthy.
然后现在受到某些东西的报复
Now something's out for revenge.
而家族中的男性就一个一个死去
And the men in their family are dying.
嘿 你认为现在马克斯也处于危险之中吗
Hey, you think Max is in danger?
让我们查查他的过去
Let's figure it out before he is.
看来我和这些人还有点共同点
Well, l know one thing I have in common with these people.
什么共同点
What's that?
我们两家都是受诅咒的
Both our families are cursed.
我们家族可不是受诅咒的
Our family's not cursed.
我们家族只是有些污点
We just had our dark spots.
就象乌云笼罩着我们家族
Our dark spots are pretty dark.
你太悲观了
You're dark.
我妈正在休息
My mom's resting.
她真的撑不下去了
She's pretty wrecked.
那很正常
Of course.
这些人接踵而来 就象大杂烩一样
All these people kept coming with, like, casseroles.
我最后还是让他们回去
I finally had to tell them all to go away.
单单的一句"我很抱歉"这根本解决不了问题
You know, because nothing says "I'm sorry" like tuna casserole.
你是怎么挨过来的
How you holding up?
我还好
I'm okay.
你父亲和你舅舅 他们关系很好吧
Your dad and your uncle were close?
我想是的
Yeah, l guess.
因为他们是兄弟
I mean, they were brothers.
我年幼的时候他们经常一起出去
They used to hang out all the time when l was little.
那最近是不没有那么频繁了
But not lately, much?
没有 还是一如既往
No, it's not that.
只是我长大后我们成为了邻居
's just We used to be neighbors when l was a kid.
我们住在镇子的对面 而罗杰舅舅就住在我们旁边
We lived across town in this house and Uncle Roger lived next door.
因此他一直和我们在一起
So he was over all the time.
原来是这样
Right.
没有发觉那屋子什么问题吗
So how was it in that house
当你还是小孩子的时候
When you were a kid?
没有
It was fine.
为什么这样问
Why?
都是美好的回忆吗
All good memories?
你还记得有什么不寻常的事吗
Do you remember anything unusual?
一些与你父亲和舅舅相关的事
Something involving your father and your uncle, maybe?
为什么你问这些
y do you ? Why do you ask?
只是随便问问而已
Just a question.
不 没有发生过什么事
No. There was nothing.
他们一直很好
We were totally normal.
是吗 那不错啊
appy. Good. That's good.
你肯定很累了
Well, you must be exhausted.
看来我们得离开了
We should take off.
是的
Right.
谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
没事
Yeah.
任何一个家庭都不可能是一直快乐的
Nobody's family is totally normal and happy.
你注意到当他提到 那老房子的时候的神情了吗
See when he was talking about his house?
他的声音让人感到他有点恐惧
He sounded scared.
马克斯并没告诉我们全部
Max isn't telling us everything.
我看我们得找到他们以前的老邻居
I say we go find the old neighborhood.
弄清楚到底米勒一家的生活是怎么样的
Find out what life was really like for the Millers.
你住在这里很长时间了吗
You lived in the neighborhood long?
大概快有20年了吧
Well, almost 20 years now.
这里环境非常优雅 清净
It's nice and quiet.
为什么要问这个 你想买这里的房子吗
Why? You looking to buy?
没有 事实上我们只想问一下你
No. We were just wondering if you might recall a family.
关于住在街对面右边那户人家的情况
That used to live right across the street.
他们姓米勒 他们有个小孩叫马克斯
The Millers. They had a little boy named Max.
没错
Right.
我还记得他们
Yeah, l remember them.
米勒的兄弟就住他们隔壁
The brother had the place next door.
你们想问什么
So, what's this about?
是关于那个可怜的小孩吗
That poor kid okay?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我这辈子还没见过如此对待自己的小孩
In my life, I've never seen a child treated like that.
我是说 我听见米勒对马克斯的喊骂
I mean, l'd hear Mr. Miller yelling.
然后把他的东西扔到大街上
And throwing things clear across the street.
米勒是个酒鬼
He was a mean drunk.
他经常把马克斯打的鼻青脸肿
He used to beat the tar out of Max.
单是手就打断过2次 这还只是我知道的
Bruises. Broke his arm two times that I know of.
米勒经常这样吗
And this was going on regularly?
几乎每天都这样
Practically every day.
其实米勒那暴力的兄弟对那孩子 也是一样拳脚相加
In fact, that thug brother of his was just as likely to take a swing at him.
但最糟的是孩子的继母
But the worst part was the stepmother.
她只是站在那里 袖手旁观
She'd just stand there, checked out.
从不去阻止他们 保护孩子
Never lifted a finger to protect him.
我叫警察来过大概有7 8次了
I must have called the police seven or eight times.
但没什么用
Never did any good.
你刚才有说到那位是继母 是吗
You said stepmother.
我想大概他生母可能死于车祸 或者其他一些事故
I think his real mom died. Some sort of accident. Car accident, l think.
你还好吧
You okay, there?
- 我还好 - 打扰你了
- Yeah. - Thanks for your time.
谢谢你所提供的资料
thank you. Come on.
天啊
God.
我不知道你在说些什么
I don't know what you mean by that.
你知道我并没做错过什么
You know l never did anything.
没错
That's right.
你什么都没做
You didn't do anything.
你从来就没有阻止过他们
You didn't stop them. Not once.
你怎么了
How did you...?
马克斯 求求你不要
Max! Please!
每次你都只是站在那里看
For every time you stood there and watched.
假装什么都没发生似的
Pretending it wasn't happening.
对不起
l'm sorry.
你不是真心的 你只是不想死而已
No, you're not. You just don't want to die.
马克斯已经下手了 就象我看见的那样
Max is doing it. Everything I've been seeing.
你确信
You're sure about this?
是的 我看见他了
Yeah, I saw him.
他怎么逃跑的
How's he pulling it off?
我不知道 这有点象心灵感应
It looked like telekinesis.
他能够通灵吗 难道他是…
He's psychic? He's a spoon bender?
我根本没有意识到 但这次我确确实实看到他了
I didn't even realize it but this whole time he was there.
他父亲死的时候他就在车库外面
Outside the garage when his dad died.
他舅舅死的时候他也在那公寓里
He was in the apartment when his uncle died.
这些画面我并未感应到米勒
These visions. l wasn't connecting to the Millers.
但我感应到了马克斯
I was connecting to Max.
但我还是不知道为什么
The thing I don't get is why, man.
我猜想是因为我们是如此的相似
I guess, because we're so alike?
你在说什么呢 那家伙根本不象你
What? He's nothing like you.
我们都有心灵感应能力
Well, we both have psychic abilities.
- 我们都有 - 都有什么
- We're both - Both what?
萨姆 马克斯是个怪物
sam He's a monster.
他杀了2个人 他现在正想杀第3个
He's killed two and he's gunning for a third.
因为那些毒打
Well, with what he went through
他在报复那些人
the beatings to want revenge on those people
很遗憾我并不这样认为
I hate to say it, but it's not that insane to want revenge on those people.
我不认为马克斯有精神疾病
I hate to say it, but it's not that insane.
那怎么会下手杀了他的家人
It doesn't justify murdering your family. Dean
他和我们以前猎杀的恶魔没什么两样
He's no different than anything else we've hunted.
我们得去阻止他
We gotta end him.
我们不能杀了马克斯
We're not going to kill Max.
那该怎么办
Then what?
难道把他拷到警察那里 跟警察讲"看住他"
Hand him over to the cops and say, "Lock him up, officer.
"这家伙用意念杀人"
He kills with the power of his mind"?
得了吧
Forget it.
这行不通
No way, man.
萨姆 迪恩
Sam Dean.
他是个人
He's a person.
我们可以和他谈谈
We can talk to him.
答应我这次让我做主
Hey, promise me you'll follow my lead on this one.
那好吧
All right, fine.
但我不会让他再伤害任何人
But l'm not letting him hurt anybody else.
你知道我并没做错过什么
You know I never did anything.
没错 你什么都没做
That's right. You didn't do anything.
你从来就没有阻止过他们
You didn't stop them. Not once.
神父
Fathers?
你们在这里干吗
What are you doing here? Uh....
很抱歉闯了进来
Sorry to interrupt.
马克斯 我们能到外面谈谈吗 就一会
Max, could we...? Could we talk to you outside for just one second?
关于什么
About what?
这里不方便说话
It's It's private.
我不想打扰你妈妈
I wouldn't want to bother your mother with it.
时间不会太久的 我保证
We won't be long at all, though. I promise.
那好吧
Okay. Great.
你们根本不是牧师
You're not priests!
马克斯 到底发生了什么
Max, what's happening?
闭嘴
Shut up.
你这是在干什么啊
What are you doing?
让你闭嘴
l said, shut up!
- 马克斯 冷静下来 - 你是谁
- Max, calm down! - Who are you?
我们只是想和你谈谈
We just wanna talk to you.
那你为什么带这个来
Right. That's why you brought this.
那是个误会 好吗
That was a mistake.
虽然我们之前撒了慌 但是我们不会再撒谎了
So was lying about who we were. But no more lying, okay?
只是想让你听我把话说完
Just, please, just hear me out.
你想说什么
About what?
我看见了那是你干的
I saw you do it.
我看见了你在你杀你父亲和舅舅之前
I saw you kill your dad and your uncle. Before it happened.
- 你说什么 - 我真的看见这样的景象 马克斯
- What? - l'm having visions, Max. About you.
你疯了
You're crazy.
难道你刚才不想用那刀子 捅向你继母吗
So you weren't gonna launch a knife at your stepmom? Right here?
我知道这很难相信 马克斯
Is it that hard to believe, Max?
但你得想想该怎么做
Look what you can do.
马克斯 我就站在这里 好吗
Max, l was drawn here, all right?
我到这里来是来帮助你的
I think I'm here to help you.
没人能帮得了我
No one can help me.
让我试试
Let me try.
我们得谈谈… 我和你
We'll just talk, me and you.
我们可以让迪恩和艾丽丝出去
We'll get Dean and Alice out of here.
- 这不行 - 没人能离开这屋子
- No way. - Nobody leaves this house.
没人能离开 好吗
And nobody has to, all right?
他们只是上楼去而已
They'll just They'll just go upstairs.
萨姆 我不会让你单独和他在一起的
Sam. I'm not leaving you alone with him.
不 我们得这样做
Yes, you are
听着 马克斯 现在这是你控制着
.Look, Max. You're in charge here, all right?
我们都很清楚
We all know that.
没有人敢违背你
No one's gonna do anything you don't wanna do.
伙计 我只说5分钟
I'm talking five minutes, here.
萨姆
Sam!
只给你5分钟
Five minutes.
快说
Go. Come on.
我不奢望我能彻底理解 你所经历的事
Look, l can't begin to understand what you went through.
说的没错 你不可能理解
That's right, you can't.
但马克斯这事应该停止了
But, Max. This has to stop.
会的 在我杀了我继母之后
It will. After my stepmother.
不 你应该让她走
No. You need to let her go.
为什么
Why?
她有打过你吗
Did she beat you?
没有 但她从来没想过救我
No. But she never tried to save me.
她是他们的同伙
She's a part of it too.
听着 他们对你的所做所为
Look, what they did to you
他们在你年幼时对你所干的事
What they all did to you growing up....
理应受到惩罚
They deserve to be punished.
只是在我年幼时吗
Growing up?
上个礼拜他们还打过我
Try last week.
我父亲一直在打我 只是不让别人看到而已
My dad still hit me. Just in places people wouldn't see it.
我想是本性难移吧
Old habits die hard, l guess.
我对这很抱歉
I'm sorry.
当我发现我可以用意念移动物体的时候
When I first found out I could move things.
我想这是上天给我的礼物
It was a gift
我的人生没有希望
My whole life, l was helpless.
但我现在有了这样的能力
But now l had this.
上个礼拜父亲又喝地烂醉如泥
So last week, Dad gets drunk. First time in a long time.
他把我往死里打
And he beats me to hell
从未如此狠毒过
First time in a long time.
然后我知道我该干什么了
And then I knew what I had to do.
你为什么不逃
Why didn't you just leave?
那根本解决不了问题
It wasn't about getting away.
他们还是会抓到我的
Just knowing that they'd still be out there.
我不想再担惊受怕了
It was about not being afraid.
当我父亲看着我时
When my Dad used to look at me
眼神里充满了厌恨
There was hate in his eyes.
你能体会到那种感觉吗
Do you know what that feels like?
- 我不能 - 他因为各种事而责骂我
- No. - He blamed me for everything.
因为他的工作 他的生活 以及我母亲的死
For his job. For his life. For my mom's death.
为什么因为你母亲的死 他要骂你
Why would he blame you for your mom's death?
因为她死在托儿所 而我正在睡觉
Because she died in my nursery, while l was asleep in my crib.
就象那是我的错误一样
As if that makes it my fault.
你母亲死在你的托儿所
She died in your nursery? Yeah.
是的 那是场火灾
There was a fire.
而他自己喝醉了乱说她死的非常奇怪
And he'd get drunk and babble on like she died in some insane way.
他说我母亲整个人烧了起来
He said that she burned up.
被定在了天花板上
Pinned to the ceiling.
听我说 马克斯
Listen to me, Max.
你父亲所说的发生在 你母亲身上的事
What your dad said about what happened to your mom...
那是真的
it's real.
你说什么
What?
我母亲也是这样死的 一模一样
It happened to my mom too. Exactly the same.
在我的托儿所 我的摇篮
My nursery. My crib.
我父亲看见她在天花板上
My dad saw her on the ceiling.
你父亲大概和我父亲一样喝醉了
Your dad must've been as drunk as mine.
没有
No
没有 真的是一模一样 马克斯
No. It's the same thing, Max.
是同一个物体杀了我们的母亲
The same thing killed our mothers.
那不可能
That's not possible.
这大概就是为什么我白天会看见 那样的景象
This must be why l've been having visions during the day.
而且它们正变的越来越糟
Why they're getting more intense.
因为你和我都有心灵感应
Because you and I must be connected in some way.
你的能力是不是6 7个月前有的
Your abilities, they started six, seven months ago, right?
因为忧郁而产生的
Out of the blue?
你是怎么知道的
How'd you know that?
因为我的能力也是那个时候产生的
Because that's when mine started.
你可能更久之前
Yours seem to be much further along
但这些不正是暗示着什么吗
But still, this means something, right?
我是说
I mean
我和你因为一些原因而被选中
For some reason, you and l.... You and I were chosen.
为什么会这样
For what?
我也不清楚
I don't know.
但迪恩 我的哥哥和我 我们正在猎捕杀我母亲的凶手
But Dean and I, my brother and l, we're hunting for your mom's killer.
我们可以找到答案 这样就能帮到我们和你
And we could find answers, answers that can help us both.
但你得让我们走 马克斯
But you gotta let us go, Max.
你得让你的继母走
You gotta let your stepmother go.
不行 他们对我的所作所为
No. What they did to me....
让我至今有噩梦
I still have nightmares.
我现在仍然一直感到恐惧 我仿佛还在等下一顿毒打
I'm still scared all the time, like I'm just waiting for that next beating.
我已经厌倦这样的生活了
I'm just tired of being scared.
如果我杀了她们 那一切都会结束
If l do this, it'll be over.
听着 别这样干
No, don't you get it?
这一切都不会结束的
It won't.
噩梦不会终结 马克斯 并不是你想象的这样
The nightmares won't end, Max. Not like this.
只会愈发的痛苦
It's just more pain.
而这也会让你变的和他们一样
And it makes you as bad as them.
马克斯 你不该一个人独自承受这一切
Max, you don't have to go through all this by yourself.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不要
No!
马克斯
Max!
别那样干 马克斯
No. Max!
马克斯
Max.
不要
No.
养的儿子… 不
Son of a.... No.
马克斯
Max.
不要. -
No.
马克斯
Max.
别动 这和你无关
Stay back. It's not about you.
如果你想杀了他 那先杀了我
You wanna kill her, you gotta go through me first.
那好吧
Okay.
不
No.
马克斯
Max.
不
No.
别动 这和你无关
Stay back. It's not about you.
如果你想杀了他 那先杀了我
You're gonna kill her, you gotta go through me first.
那好吧
Okay.
不 别样干 求你了
No, don't! Don't! Please.
求你了 马克斯
Please, Max.
马克斯 让我们来帮你 好吗
Max We can help you, all right?
你现在的所作所为
But this, what you're doing...
它并不会是好的结局
it's not the solution.
它不会改变什么
It's not gonna fix anything.
你说的没错
You're right.
不
No!
马克斯攻击我
Max attacked me.
他用枪威胁我
He threatened me with a gun.
那这两位
And these two?
他们是我们的朋友
They're family friends.
当马克斯来的时候 我把他们叫来
I called them as soon as Max arrived.
我有点恐惧
I was scared.
他们想要阻止他
They tried to stop him.
他们因为那枪而打起来
They fought for the gun.
马克斯是从哪里得到枪的
Where did Max get the gun?
我不知道
I don't know.
他拿出枪 然后…
He showed up with it, and he....
没事了米勒太太
It's all right, Mrs. Miller.
我失去了所有的亲人
I've lost everyone.
那好吧 如果我们有问题 会立即打电话给你的
Okay. We'll call if we have more questions.
谢谢
Thanks, officer.
走吧
Come on.
如果我说些其他的 而不那样说的话
If l'd just said something else....Gotten through to him somehow.
别继续那样了
Oh, don't do that.
继续什么
Do what?
继续自责
Torture yourself.
这与你说的没什么关系
It wouldn't have mattered.
马克斯真的无法挽救
Max was too far gone.
当我刚才想起他看我的眼神
When I think about how he looked at me, man, right before.
我想我该干点什么
I should have done something.
得了吧 伙计 你拿你的命在冒险
Come on, man. You risked your life.
我是说 可能我们该早20年到这里
I mean, yeah, maybe if we'd gotten there 20 years earlier.
告诉你一件事
Well, l'll tell you one thing.
我们很幸运有父亲
We're lucky we had Dad.
我从没想到这话出自你口
I never thought l'd hear you say that.
自从妈妈死后我们的路 就开始变的完全不同了
Well, he could have gone a whole other way after Mom.
如果不是一直在猎杀恶魔的话
A little more tequila, a little less demon hunting...
那我们的童年就会和马克斯一样
then we would have had Max's childhood.
不管怎么说 我们现在还能这样
All things considered we turned out okay.
还得感谢父亲
Thanks to him.
是啊
All things considered.
迪恩 我正在想
Dean, l've been thinking.
现在没一件事好事
That's never a good thing.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我正在考虑
I've been thinking
不管这个恶魔是什么
Why would this demon, or whatever it is...
它杀了母亲 杰西卡和马克斯的母亲 这是为了什么
why would it kill Mom and Jessica and Max's mother, you know?
它想要什么
What does it want?
不清楚 你不觉得它可能在跟踪我们
No idea.Well, you think maybe it was after us?
又或者跟着马克斯吗
After Max and me?
你为什么会这样想
Why would you think that?
大概可能因为我和他都有心灵感应吧
I mean, either telekinesis or premonitions...
我们都有这种能力 这你知道吗
we both had abilities, you know?
可能也许是其他原因它才跟着我们
Maybe it was after us for some reason.
萨姆 如果它单是只想杀你 那不是轻而易举吗
Sam. lf it wanted you, it would've just taken you. Okay?
现在这事不是你的错
This is not your fault. Okay? This is not your fault.
这与你无关
It's not about you.
那和谁有关
Then what is it about?
这与那些恶魔对我们家 所干的事有关
It's about that damn thing that did this to our family.
我们要找到它们 然后杀了它们
That thing that we're gonna find and kill.
就那么多
And that's all.
事实上还有其他事
Actually, there's something else too.
噢 你在说什么呢
Oh, jeez. What?
当马克斯把我关在壁橱里
When Max locked me in that closet
并用那大橱堵住门
With that big cabinet against the door...
我移开了它
l moved it.
你的上肢力量比我想象的大
You got more upper body strength than l gave you credit for.
不是这样的 伙计 我用意念移动了它 就象马克斯那样
No, man. I moved it. Like Max.
喔 是吗
Oh. Right.
是
Right.
是的
Yeah.
让这弯曲
Bend this.
我无法收发自如 迪恩
l can't turn it on and off, Dean.
那好 你是怎么做的
How'd you do it?
我不清楚 我还不能控制它
I don't know. I can't control it. l just....
我看见你死的情景
I saw you die
然后这种力量就从我身体里涌了出来
and it just came out of me. Like a Like a punch.
就象一个怪物般
You know? Like a freak adrenaline thing.
我想应该这事还会发生的
Well, l'm sure it won't happen again.
有可能
Yeah, maybe.
伙计 你担心吗 你担心我会变成象马克斯一样
Aren't you worried that l could turn into Max
或者其他人
or something?
不 不可能 你知道为什么吗
Nope. No way. You know why?
不知道 为什么
No. Why?
你有马克斯所没有的优势
You've got one advantage Max didn't.
你是指父亲
Dad?
但父亲不在这 Dean
Because Dad's not here, Dean.
不 是指我
No. Me.
只要我还在
As long as l'm around
那些坏事就不可能发生在你身上
Nothing bad is gonna happen to you.
现在我知道你的预兆有什么用了
Now, then. I know what we need to do about your premonitions.
我知道我们该去哪里了
I know where we have to go.
哪里
Where?
维加斯
Vegas.
别这样 走吧 伙计
What? Come on, man.
去赌两把 我们可以发大财了
Craps tables? We'd clean up.